<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>This week, I learned – weeknotes by Mo Morgan</title>
    <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com" />
    <updated>2023-01-27T18:38:33+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Mo Morgan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://twil.momorgan.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0004</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0004/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0004/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-27T18:38:33+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A long old trip to a clients’ site on Monday: a seven-hour round trip by rail. Up early, home late. A good day, though. And I’ve learned there’s no such thing as train-grade wifi anymore. Some appauling, others practically as good as home. And there&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0003</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0003/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0003/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-22T22:07:10+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Went househunting. No matter how carefully you study the listings and photos, you never know what awaits you. Perhaps I was seduced by the Rightmove ad: soft, twinkling sunlight streaming in as soft, twinkling piano music plays on. But I certainly wasn’t prepared for the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0002</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0002/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0002/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-22T22:06:08+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A thought about weeknotes, why they’d be valuable for agencies and yet why they’ll never adopt them, follows below. So I’ve been doing a bunch of research in recent weeks into the automotive market and its aspirations to move from product manufacture to service provider.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0001</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0001/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0001/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-22T22:06:23+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hey. It’s me. Hope you’re well. A longer introduction to this little site will follow below. For wider context, I also wrote about my 2022. I bought a bass guitar! The build-up to this has been long. 20 years ago I was in a garage&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>2022 Yearnote</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/2022-yearnote/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/2022-yearnote/</id>

        <updated>2023-01-22T22:05:59+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There are years we’d rather forget, and them some we wish to cherish. 2022 has been a significant and transformative year for me, particularly considering the two or three that came before it. Here’s some of the things that happened. First, a brief primer on&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
</feed>
