<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>This week, I learned – weeknotes by Mo Morgan</title>
    <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com" />
    <updated>2023-03-03T18:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Mo Morgan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://twil.momorgan.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0009</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0009/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0009/</id>

        <updated>2023-03-03T18:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Difficult week, this one. And difficult to write about, too. This is one of those occasions when working in the open is incompatible with things that are not for public consumption. So this weeknote’s a little light. Went to the dentist on Saturday, for two&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0008</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0008/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0008/</id>

        <updated>2023-02-24T18:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Offer accepted on the house, so that process is underway. I’m starting to think about the practicalities that’ll make it possible to do the work to bring it all up to standard. Despite having a paved front drive, it’s not long enough for my 23ft-long&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0007</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0007/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0007/</id>

        <updated>2023-02-17T18:00:00+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The Last of Us is an impressive show. That third episode with Nick Offerman and Murray Bartlett putting down world-class performances of a great script had me bawling. A working week of wacky weirdness. Knotty strategic problems. If there is a perfect answer, it’s not&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0006</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0006/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0006/</id>

        <updated>2023-02-10T18:53:34+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    A slog of a week. One of those ones that felt about nine days long. Not always a bad thing, though. Another unsuccessful house-hunt at the weekend. Couldn’t get in to see the one I’m sure is probably the best candidate so far. Another was&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0005</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0005/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0005/</id>

        <updated>2023-02-10T18:15:29+00:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I now have an NHS dentist that works Saturdays! Never had much luck with dental administration, either finding them available or them honouring my appointments, so being able to go on a weekend appointment feels like a special thing. Therefore, I went for an inspection&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
</feed>
