<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>This week, I learned – weeknotes by Mo Morgan</title>
    <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com" />
    <updated>2023-07-08T16:11:03+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Mo Morgan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://twil.momorgan.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0027</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0027/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0027/</id>

        <updated>2023-07-08T16:11:03+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Delighted to have gotten hold of a newly-reintroduced Sound Burger turntable. I’ve wanted one of these forever, decades maybe, but wasn’t quite brave enough to take on a well-loved second-hander. It’s small enough to sit on my desk so I can put albums on as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0026</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0026/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0026/</id>

        <updated>2023-06-30T18:00:00+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Apart from in college and an ill-judgement during a lockdown, I’ve never bothered trying to be clean-shaven. Another lockdown ill-judgement was to try and grow a ‘proper’ beard, but the two sides of my face are yet to reach an agreement about whether it should&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0025</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0025/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0025/</id>

        <updated>2023-06-24T08:45:25+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    From Osaka, flew to Ho Chi Minh City. The first thing that’s striking is the traffic: there are road signals and markings, but herds of cars submerged in swarms of mopeds pay little attention. The next striking thing is the humidity, and the third is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0024</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0024/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0024/</id>

        <updated>2023-06-24T08:15:02+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Still in Japan. Next stop: Kanazawa. Japanese hotels, I’m finding, don’t have wardrobes. They have a rail, parallel to one wall, with four coathangers. Travelling with about a weeks’ worth of evermore crumpled clothing, I’d love to let the air get at it. My t-shirts&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Weeknote 0023</title>
        <author>
            <name>Mo Morgan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0023/"/>
        <id>https://twil.momorgan.com/weeknote-0023/</id>

        <updated>2023-06-24T08:15:20+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It’s a travel-writing cliché to call somewhere a place of contrasts, so let’s get that out of the way. Tokyo is a place of contrasts, didn’t you know? It has a rich history and tradition, cheek-by-jowl with modernity. There, that’s done. The same also applies&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
</feed>
